Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Whalen, Lucille, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3476 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., ca. 1970; nam_ua950.003-3477 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3478 (Box 41, Folder 49)
- Wharton, Clifton R., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3479 (Box 41, Folder 50)
- Wheeler, Paul Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3480 (Box 41, Folder 51)
- Wheeler, Paul F., 1961; nam_ua950.003-3481 (Box 41, Folder 52)
- Wheeler, Paul F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3482 (Box 41, Folder 53)
- Whitaker, Judith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3483 (Box 41, Folder 54)
- Whitaker, Judith Gage, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3484 (Box 41, Folder 55)
- Whitbeck, Caroline, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3485 (Box 41, Folder 56)
- Whitby, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3486 (Box 41, Folder 57)
- White, Gary W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3487 (Box 41, Folder 58)
- White, James L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3488 (Box 41, Folder 59)
- White, Ronald K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3489 (Box 41, Folder 60)
- Whitford, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3490 (Box 41, Folder 61)
- Whitney, Willard Hall, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3491 (Box 41, Folder 62)
- Whittaker, Tatyana I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3492 (Box 41, Folder 63)
- Whitten, William B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3493 (Box 41, Folder 64)
- Wiest, Nailene Chou, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3494 (Box 41, Folder 65)
- Wilbanks, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3495 (Box 41, Folder 66)
- Wilbur, W. Allan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3496 (Box 41, Folder 67)
- Wiles, David K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3497 (Box 41, Folder 68)
- Wilken, Donald R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3498 (Box 41, Folder 69)
- Wilken, Donald R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3499 (Box 41, Folder 70)
- Wilkie, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3500 (Box 41, Folder 71)
- Wilkie, Richard W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3501 (Box 41, Folder 72)
- Wilkins, Leslie T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3502 (Box 41, Folder 73)
- Wilkins, Leslie T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3503 (Box 41, Folder 74)
- Williams, Catherine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3504 (Box 41, Folder 75)
- Williams-Myers, A.J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3505 (Box 41, Folder 76)
- Williams, Fannie B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3506 (Box 41, Folder 77)
- Williams, James R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3507 (Box 41, Folder 78)
- Williams, Lois Virginia, 1948-1979; nam_ua950.003-3508 (Box 41, Folder 79)
- Williams, Marianne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3509 (Box 41, Folder 80)
- Williams, P.F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3510 (Box 41, Folder 81)
- Williams, Sara, 1988; nam_ua950.003-3511 (Box 41, Folder 82)
- Williams, Sara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3512 (Box 41, Folder 83)
- Williams, Sara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3513 (Box 41, Folder 84)
- Williamson, Wanda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3514 (Box 41, Folder 85)
- Wilsey, Neal, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3515 (Box 41, Folder 86)
- Wilson, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3516 (Box 41, Folder 87)
- Winarsky, Norman D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3517 (Box 41, Folder 88)
- Winkelman, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3518 (Box 41, Folder 89)
- Winkler, Wm. S., 1968; nam_ua950.003-3519 (Box 41, Folder 90)
- Winn, Hudson, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3520 (Box 41, Folder 91)
- Winn, Hudson Sumner, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3521 (Box 41, Folder 92)
- Winn, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3522 (Box 41, Folder 93)
- Winter, Gene, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3523 (Box 41, Folder 94)
- Winters, William G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3524 (Box 41, Folder 95)
- Wissel, Peter A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3525 (Box 41, Folder 96)
- Wittenborg, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3526 (Box 41, Folder 97)
- Wittowski, Wolfgang, 1986; nam_ua950.003-3527 (Box 41, Folder 98)
- Woefel, Joseph D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3528 (Box 41, Folder 99)
- Wolfe, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3529 (Box 41, Folder 100)
- Woo, Louis K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3530 (Box 41, Folder 101)
- Wood, Ann L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3531 (Box 41, Folder 102)
- Wood, Ann L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3532 (Box 41, Folder 103)
- Wood, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3533 (Box 41, Folder 104)
- Woodbury, John R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3534 (Box 41, Folder 105)
- Woolsworth, Samuel B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3535 (Box 41, Folder 106)
- Wright, Gary A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3536 (Box 41, Folder 107)
- Wright, J. Ward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3537 (Box 41, Folder 108)
- Wright, Leonard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3538 (Box 41, Folder 109)
- Wright, Nathan Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3539 (Box 41, Folder 110)
- Wright, Nathan Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3540 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Wright, Theodore, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3541 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Wundt, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3542 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Yang, Chung Shu, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3543 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Yeaton, Kelly, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3544 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Yerburgh, Mark R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3545 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Yoels, William C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3546 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Yohalem, Francoise, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3547 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Yokoyama, Elaine Itsuko, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3548 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- York, George Morell, 1916-1947; nam_ua950.003-3549 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- York, G.M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3550 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- York, George H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3551 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- York, Roy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3552 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Young, Michael, 1998-1999; nam_ua950.003-3553 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Young, Samuel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3554 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Young, William F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3555 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Young, William F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3556 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Yuki, Gary, 1987; nam_ua950.003-3557 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Yum, June Ock, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3558 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Yun, Kwan Koo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3559 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Yuter, Alan J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3560 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Zacek, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3561 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Zacharias, Jerrold R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3562 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Zahavi, Gerald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3563 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Zauber, Raisa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3564 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Zazzau, Vivien E., ca. 2002-2010; nam_ua950.003-3565 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Zeh, Robert M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3566 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Zeigler, Bernard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3567 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Zeller, Phil, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3568 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Zendle, Hal, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3569 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Zilles, Luke, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3570 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Zimmerman, Barry J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3571 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3572 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3573 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3574 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3575 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3576 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Zimmerman, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3577 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3578 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3579 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Zimmerman, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3580 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Zimmerman, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3581 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Zimmerman, Sanford, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3582 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Zimmermann, Virgil B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3583 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Zimmers, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3584 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Zubieta, Jon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3585 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Zubrick, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3586 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Zuckerman, Jerold J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3587 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Zwana, Japhet M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3588 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Zwana, Japhet M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3589 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Zwarich, Ronald J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3590 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Zych, Maria, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3591 (Box 42, Folder 52)